SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right, all right.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Okay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let me just read, make sure I understand what's supposed to happen next.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: You ready? Uh, yes. There's... Okay. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, um, all right, so you, you, um...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You have now secured, so Solomon Nedrzak has given you a spell book. Let me give you that spell book Nicholas.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: which you can cast as I think you can cast them as spells but you can cast them as scrolls so let's say you can cast them as scrolls all right
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
UNKNOWN: Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Where is it?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Nick, where should I put this in Discord, I guess?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right, where am I? The original, no? I mean, you know... All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You get a potion of greater healing, and he also provides you the following swirls.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm listening. Okay, they're in the D&D chat, in the Discord chat. Okay, do you see them?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Blug, Yasha's Song, Athol, God. Thank you. Alrighty.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So the situation as it is, is that you now have secured your allies.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: But all of the allies are going to help you after you get rid of Dengor.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Giants
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's the giant of Sith Morcane. I thought it would do that.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you got me. Was you the Reverend Pope of Thatcher?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Shouldn't the revenant be there because that's what she thinks there? The revenant has gone on a lunatic
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Who's going on a lunatic bitch? Yeah, but shouldn't she be there because that's what she thinks killed it?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: She isn't here right now.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: okay so there is another giant that also so let me explain yes
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There this okay so you should remind you what's going on the Sith Morcane is currently being the Sith Morcane currently has a forge
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yeah, before just Surtr.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: which is dedicated to some demonic giant god, not important.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: what's been going on is they've been building materials that they've been shipping to Miramindra that they're going to use to stay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You managed to stop one of those transfers.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: um every all the factions in Mare Medra are willing I'm in Sith Morcane
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: are willing to help you as long as you get rid of the current giants that are running the show.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You said plural? Yes, plural.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what you've gotten rid of was the fire giant that was taking the... How many fire giants are we talking about?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: How many fire giants are we talking about?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Um, excuse me, an undetermined amount.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: You know, this is a good question.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Why did we have to go to the floor, brother?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: what did we get back? what? nothing. what did we actually get out of doing all that?
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Well, so you're trying to take over Maerimydra. Yes, and otherwise that's helpful for us.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I aspire my world will be the last of the suns. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So, no, no, no, no, I mean, let me, Nick, okay, so, so let me remind you, you, you, you managed to
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Get the, the, the dragon, the dragon, the dragon fire giants from Nerevator.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we managed to get the fire right, right? The fire giants.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Solom the Vethersack
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Cast the spell, does his thing with the firetrap. Yay! We'll beat you down.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You're now feeding yourself, you now hear from, uh, you now get information from them around you.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: From the Emerald Enclave and your various allies and the Mind Flayers.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: right that we needed to do in my mind for breaking up yes and what you've learned is
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: that the fire giants are building these devices that they're going to use to lay waste on the surface world.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: oh right we need this yes and so then so while you so your job was to go and do something
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Something about that. Right. While you were going down there to do something about that you met Alder.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: A halfling rogue who notoriously imprisoned Lolth.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and she explained that she sent a whole bunch of
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and a bunch of other adventures into Metzl-Barbansan.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, but she didn't realize there was another problem.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: One of the demons, Grast, had a backup plan. He was going to show up at Mirambedra. Okay. Right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So her, the original plan was she, she, the original plan and she was
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Going great was that a whole bunch of heroes were going to go into the Underdark.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: They were very close to putting together a plan which was going to attract all of the demons
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and to Menzo-Buronson where they would all die and the problem with the demons would just go away.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: but what she noticed but what happened was
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: took another way yeah she discovered that Grast may have another plan and so you became her plan b V.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: of course to go into Nerevidra and make sure that a grass shows up
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Grasp is defeated.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Your concerns are, you need to get into their midriffs.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: To stop rest. Whether Mavigdala belongs to the Fire Giants or not.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There's a problem for another day, right? Just to keep that in mind.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: um but you also like to destroy Nerevidra because that's where the fire giants are currently if grass if grass shows up
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It doesn't really matter, right? He's powerful enough that he's going to cause chaos and mayhem with or without
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: magical devices but if you can defeat him
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: then the and your allies can destroy enough of Maerimydra and the threat of the Fire Giants
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The disease-infected phylogenase goes away. Okay. The other theory you have is that...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Fire Giants are, have been driven insane by Rust.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So if you defeat Grast, they'll be less crazy.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so they might be more reasonable. They might be less willing to cause mayhem and chaos.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Fragments. The Fragments are not, you know...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: They're, they're, they're, they're, yeah, but they're not unreasonable. How could I put it that way?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they're violence, but they're not insane.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: these guys are sort of like fire giants to the 20th degree yeah right so
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's more of extreme fire giant than normal fire giant.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And so the way to think about it is that the fire giants have been driven mad by grass.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You need to defeat the fire giants and more importantly you need to make sure that if Brass shows up, you defeat him.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I know how the story ends. Well, you've been facing grass left, right, and center.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Right? Yeah. And so don't you want to have one last chance at it? Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No? Well, not after a war.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, again, remember, everybody has got objectives.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So, the people in Hillsfar... Do you know what would have done? What would have said to them?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: that grass killed Solom Owlbear, Owlbear, Owlbear
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: It was a good opportunity. Yes, it was.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know if the memory's failed. You know, maybe. I don't know.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, all right.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I don't think I have any further questions, so the point is we have a leave to play, a leave in.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Overbred. What? The win, the reward to do all that is that we have the Overbred. Yes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Drast is no longer inside of, you know, the demons are sent back to where they came from. What you found out was...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: that the demons were brought back into the because of some magical effect known as the blink
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: whose origin is unknown.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It was from Thanos. What? It was from Thanos. Yes, that's true.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: That's where I got the idea, isn't it? Yep. That's pretty good enough.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Veth, Rilira, Korkun, Plink
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I was thinking the lights, the Faerzess went on and off, that's where I got it, but I probably...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: My choice of the word that the blink comes from there. Yeah, right. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I was a pretty cool man. I was very impressed with myself.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: impressed with myself for stealing a good idea i'm sorry no i'm not not i'm not you shouldn't be sorry better than you should be proud of yourself actually yeah
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so, um, according to, I just wanted to say something before I join, sorry.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: According to the best information Mousavias Quilburn has,
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There were a total of 12 fire giants.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: two are dead so we have ten to kill well hold on
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Right, and so the one thing you know about fire giants is that if you kill off the head, the rest fall.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: okay right you've already spooked them out by killing two of their butler
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So if you just killed the Dengor...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: They're the lead fire giants. Okay, we... You could get that they might just run away.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: run away or join our own no that they would very unlikely
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Well, we had many, many, many likes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I just said, I said, you know, I was going to say no, and then I was like.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: We have the Stone of Giants, we have the Persec, we have the Owlbear, we have the Five that have lost.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There's many unlikings and I don't know if there's any unlikings in this. I mean, there's the whole I don't understand who the lich is.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yes? And what ghosts are?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The whole, um, we had to do a deal with it. The whole deal with the arcane. Yes, there's been a lot of...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's ups and downs. It's ups and downs in this adventure. All right. So, you're going to say that.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: We're not passionate enough to succeed.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, so, um...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So there's two ways into his palace.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay. The first way is through his palace directly. Great.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The second way is you could enter through the fame of Lolth.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You've been there before. It was that big cavern dungeon that looked like a spider, now known as the Forge of Surtr.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: oh that one yes i was i was thinking about the way we are already
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So those are your two choices. He says to get into there.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Melosavaya says he can cast a gaseous form.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: so you can enter it through the tunnels yeah okay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to do that, or do you want to go through the main door? Hell, let's go through the gatchas for a minute.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Guess his form method? Yeah, I guess. I would suggest him in the door.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I think that's really good. Good.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: One thing you do know is that this is where you're going to find all the weapons you need for Rilira.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: right so she's not so they're not so so you're that's your final we're going to go through the fate of love i get you
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and a couple of Dresden Treff.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, we're all ready.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, we need to...
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no. You need to stay too far into the middle.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Booty Okay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you arrive, okay, I know, I've read enough about this so I can now roll on it, okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So now you are going to go into the House Morcane's ruins.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Right? And there...
UNKNOWN: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Give me a moment, guys, because I have to load something.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I had something. I thought I had loaded something, but I had not. My bad.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Let's go to the center, quick, quick, quick.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Right.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Okay. Whoa. Wait a second.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what else we have here.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So you manage to you could turn into gaseous form and as a result of the gaseous form you're able to
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Sneak in to the Forge of Surtr. Great.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Forge of Surtr is...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: the thing that the thing that uh that you immediately you immediately realize
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: This is big, right? This is like not some small...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Vanilla Operation, so let me just show you what it looks like.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: You guys should see that, right? Yes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so relatively, you know, and
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: What is it that you're, what else do you see here?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The heat hits before the light does, then both at once.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: that cavern the size of a keeps great hall ceilings lost in smoke the floor grid of forged channels were mold
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and Ron, controlled by Azer, move around the heat like they were born from it, because they were. On the western wall of the road,
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All finished frames, steels and dark wood, each one of eight feet long and shaped like a sheath, cross-footed with a serpent's jaw.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The three are crated and stacked near loading dock at the far end. Four more are half assembled on the floor.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Ringing rings not set. The Azer don't look up. They are not curious. They are busy working.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The scale, this is industrial, not a workshop.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: This is a major production thing. The engines that you've...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: told about are easily identifiable they're oversized the lista or hellfire project files
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You do notice that the serpents are designed as usual.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You've noticed the crates from the previous show.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And you notice four that are still unfinished.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Thanks
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Right, uh, okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you guys, we'll push you guys.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you guys for your time.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: you guys sort of emerge over there all right
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You can see that this, if you can destroy the forge, or at least destroy the people who are manning the forge, you'll...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You'll break the fire giant's ability to build more of the siege weapons. Don't throw a beer bottle at it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I've hated to work the wands. Oh, cool. I'm very old. That's what it is. It is.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Ah, I rolled with her, but never mind.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I legitimately throw up your model on it. That's the best. It worked once, it worked again. We're gonna have to get into a fight.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So what if that's a Molotov cocktail? Um, Molotov? Did you say Molotov cocktail? Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: that's another option yeah can we do a roll for something no i don't think so
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: But how to make a log of property?
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So, um, okay, so there are four Azer...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Aqualites, two Azer priests, one Helmed Horror, and two Salamanders.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Doesn't it sound like too much? Uh, no.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so do you want to take them out?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: That's a good question.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it would be good to stop the production.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: but if we just go kill the main guy there's not going to be production right? what? if we go keep the main part designed
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There's not going to be a production, right? Yes, we don't actually know where he is.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So we don't have to go there and ask them for their keys. Is that your plan? Yes. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You're going to go, that is your plan, right? Did you agree with the plan? Mm-hmm. Great. I just want to make sure that that is the plan.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, yeah, okay.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Let me just put everything that's here.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Awesome. Let me just see if I can...
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we've... So we're not just one spirit you're gonna wear, right?
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry? Paladin of Armageddon is the one speaking dead in a way, right? The one speaking... Oh! Uh-oh! Hahaha!
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: i think my question was fake no no it is it is it is i'm just i'm just trying to like uh i'm just i just need to um
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I just, what you're seeing me is I'm trying to add colors to these guys so you know who they are.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So that's what the stats are going to be for the rest of it.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Mm-hmm.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So should we roll our initiative or are they going to be talkative?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I'll put everybody down so you can make an informed decision. Okay. What are they?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: And are these all fire guns? Nope. No. No fire guns in here. No.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: What are they? I'm about to unread the spread in a second.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The ones without the red, right?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Mm-hmm. They're Azer Acolytes, okay?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: 43, uh 46 each oh it's like one spirit guardian right
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We're with a good roll, yes, and the Azer priests are more powerful.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There. Definitely a buff here. There's the Helm of Horror.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and a number of fire salamanders.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Surtr, Juli, Faust
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: what's there to these days okay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: My own order is standing over here. Okie dokie.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You guys sort of are seeing the scene from over here.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: What is it that you wish to do? To the north over here, it is a double-
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: A little door that is giant-sized, just to make sure you know what are these? Firesounders.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Goodbye
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Really?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you very much.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay. So what is your move?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Good question. Should we ask Veth again for other stories we can find with Zayin?
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you could do that. I must even if you want to do that.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: And we want to ask the guide to come with the containers for your sign in please.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Or I can just organize it, like move it around for a while.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and all the post-competitive state examples.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Wait, can I have a toast to Bramgrim's tour site? Yeah, you can have a seat, Trish.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, that you won't be able to.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's a hell of a world.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: um it's a you've met one of those
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There are constructs that are obedient wizards.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And to other, uh... So, if you could be talkative? Uh, generally not.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: oh i have a great spell to actually just like kill with the fire dragon so the only other
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Can I cast an eye spell and maybe I just go like looking around? Yeah, you can cast the arcane eye.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Well, random question, can I put a stone in it?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Like, just like, tie on a little stone, you know.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: What does it mean when I'm accomplished, brother? I wouldn't want to accomplish it, but I basically want to have like an eye look.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I can go fly around and ask you from distance, hey, where's the, uh, that we're talking about?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Do we have a vague idea of where it is or is there anyone to like no no no no she do know where he is he's either in here
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Orhin, his palace, which was, and the entrance to his palace is three steps down the stairs. Oh, yeah, I'm going to pass our canine and go to a quick one of it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, is that what you- yeah, I'm sorry, yeah, yeah, you do, you- Oh, okay, yeah, I'm gonna cast Arcane Eye. They'll know exactly where he is. Yeah, I'm gonna go cast Arcane Eye and look where he is.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All righty.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and Barrett.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, and then I can just cast Pass Without Trace there. Oh, yeah, it's easy.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, this is ridiculous. And then the black tentacles, because that seems like a useful skill to me on a fire plan.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: sure is it though yeah i'll do it you still have to deal with these guys when we're here eventually
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Because they're not fire dregs.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: So, I will just leave this in a little bit for you to read. Yeah. If you don't mind, we'll go through.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you, I'm just telling you, I'm just telling you, these guys, these guys over here, Mike.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: It could be a problem, but I just want you to keep going. The whole lasts for an hour.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Don't let it go up. It's a quick one-and-a-half-minute show.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I could not fully explain whose first love story it was, but I don't know if I can do it again. Okay, that's fine, that's fine. Alright, bye-bye.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Where is it? What happened, D20?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Well, I have a... You want to go to the day store? Oh, right, right, right, right. Probably, sir.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: No, that was the name that you must have got.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I need a kiss. I'm good.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Tell me what the duration of an arcana is.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: One hour. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: There's a fire giant-sized door over here. I think you need to send your... You want to send it there first?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You send it there first and it's nowhere, he's nowhere to be found. Down the stairs. Down the stairs?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Stairs
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Down the stairs leads to another cave.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm going to leave these right here.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I'm reading up the map.
UNKNOWN: Kostadis Roussos: Thanks
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Your magic eye leads you down to here.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I'm sure they would be quickly gathered in the palace.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Is there a fire giant? Yes, there is. Is it a piece of fire giant? Yes, there is.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Um...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Cast path blocks to get to a place where I can avoid doing bad content in front of you.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And you guys can, if you guys can sneak across.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: there's my fast wall means you to go creates a whole event teleport spell
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You have artificer abilities to create magic, you have cast, you have
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Pass Without Trace, you have a wide variety of techniques and skills.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You have gaseous form. You can cast another instance of gaseous form. Would that work for all of us?
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and I'm still selling.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Alright, can I do this Assassin's Creed style where I gather all the enemies up into a ball and then cast sleep on them?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: So gaseous form.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it's from... Okay, so what I can do, hold on, what I can do is...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I can it can make the fall in the middle there they just read about the gaseous one's belt so they cast the outfit the magic users
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Morcevaeus is Magic Duhr's cast of Gaseous Beaumont.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We can say that up to here you're all in gases form except for about four.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: To cast Arcane Eye, you have to go... Yeah, and then I can just pass.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's the world again. We're using every single one of these pro books right now. Alright. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and there's no doubt there's one. Is that what your plan is? Yeah. Okay, so your plan is to basically...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Float along as a gas.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Uh... You... Loads.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Solvang, Azbe, Gaseous, Spore
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay. And then, uh, we arrive in King's House.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: right so we're going to move down here and put some of that
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: They're a little bit boxier than words.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Alright. What on…
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he burns and then kill him. What? He burns.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: They're all dead birds.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: We can do that? The birds. They're annoying. They're annoying.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Right. We'll make people. Thanks.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know, there's like four Hellhound boarders.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: that are kind of like so he's sleeping over here and
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: you know he's sleeping over here and he's got edgar over here
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: A couple of Narns would be here. Of course there's other people.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And that's in addition, in addition.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to see if you can start doing that.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So we can go inside this painting? What? So we can go inside this painting?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: um one guy on that like right there would be like one place over you could yeah so let me just one
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Square Over, like I really appreciate that, really.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Now that you made it like so obvious that that's where you would escape wanting to be Like, you know how much you would make my life
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: It's so much easier.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Ever black tentacles. So coming out of the tentacles, so when it was ground again, we would
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: that you can see where sin reigns, but for the race of these chemists to go from the goddess of discipline to reign, each fusion that area of
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: On a field that takes 3d6 bludgeoning damage and it has the same condition until the spell ends.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I believe you can also make the saves to end this war and and it's turned out a creature but make the third save only
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and one for Krim. Those strange creatures can take an action to make a strange plot of strife against their forebees, which ignites me.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I feel it's really a fire time just to see if I can be like, every time, that's not going to be good, the fire time just wants to know what's happening in the world.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so maybe we don't want to do that.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: They really don't want to do that and they really feel it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so this is where Dengor is.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Then the flowers become of the blue of the sun and the wind and the wind, and for the thousands of years the wind and the wind of the sun and the wind of the sun, and the wouldn't be to be useful for us all.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And just so that, because this is, can't be this easy at first.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Veth, Grimm, Sibyl. But you have potential allies. When? I'm about to show you.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So just to be clear, this encounter has potential islands. You just have to know where to get them.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: You also have Mr. Name.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: All our lessons will be in the next video.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so there are two fire giants and three stone giants.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The fire advance are clearly the past semesters here.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And the stone giants are clearly in shackles.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Boom.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I have a really funny idea. What? Yes, here it goes.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you very much, Nadia.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yep, you can do whatever you want. I don't need a sign.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's the Cuddle of the Sundance, so you can blink. Okay, go. Just go for it. Tell me what it is. Uh.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Can somebody pass Pass Without Trace for me so I can basically...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Because I have an idea because it lasts for one minute. My idea is I tap, blink, run, uh, run over
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh like get over have some cats please blink get cut the one stone giant please
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Go back into Azer, run over, cut another one loose.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, do you have control over where the link lands you? Uh, it's like...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Well, uh, it wasn't a hire, he's Anderson, he's gonna play, so, so, yeah, Dior.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: at the start of your next turn, and when the spell ends, you're, uh...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I'm not sure if I say it's your choice, but I do think we see some tendency to the space advantage.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Anarcho-Plexix, Nervous, Sender, Granger, Eupyr, and the nearest Anarcho-Plexix Okay, so you have real control over the exit. Thank you. Thank you for that.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So, welcome to your park. My idea is I...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: My idea is that I, basically, I want to
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Dross out against these devils like the Kree does, have Pass Without Trace. Fine, get over.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh try and get over and cut and cut to each one of the stone giant sleuths secretly
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you very much.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Where'd you go? Oh, hold on. I don't have time for this question. I'll be back. Okay. Thank you.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: you're in gaseous form so where's the closest spot to the giants i can drop out without anyone noticing
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Um, I don't remember. I will be good. I'll be done.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Actually, that might work if we drop out, we have a round for the rest of the minute. I mean, the thing is, the giants will get soaked.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Roll your insight or investigation.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Insider Investigation. Which one?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We'll turn it on tomorrow. Oh, sorry, sorry. All right. 22. All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You have a couple of insights. One is that the two fire giants are looking very boring.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, they're not looking at the contacts, yeah. Yes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You also can hear the fire giants snoring in the background.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you, sir, that's good. I might want to cut this.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Would there be any disadvantage it has if it's asleep and I cast a spell that kind of makes it break?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Would it automatically fail or it's going to fail if I can?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: If it's incapacitated, it's whatever the rules are for incapacitated.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Did I say good automatic hysteria? Yeah, I mean, unless it's, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: What kind of a, let me just check the condition, incapacitated.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Fiendishen, and Capacitated.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You can't take any action bonus. If you are incapacitated, you have disadvantage on the roll.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: your concentration doesn't oh it's okay if you don't want what
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I have two very useful things to do, and I don't want to cut the stun gems, please do that, because we have a very unique opportunity with the fire dine. Okay.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I might just like literally start teleporting around different ways.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Sound like a lot. We're way back. Thank you.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We're actually in Daffodil, right? Yep. So we can all move near the sun to aliens. Yep.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Careful and breathe in and make a little higher than just what I did. Hold on. I just want to make sure that he wants to go near a gaseous form.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: You can't touch anything. Yes, I know. We have something.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, make a distraction.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Not all of us because... No, I have another idea.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So the rest goes in front of Veth, then in C.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Vethu. Right. And we have a total of five days of teleportation.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Actually, can I say my idea? Yeah, you can say it again. My idea is that...
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I believe that because it's incapacitated, because it's asleep, I can give it to her.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I think that's a spell and it'll give it the uh but they'll cause it to take damage and it'll also give it the risk
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Velsar, Jynxur, Stancredition and other creatures around it, you stand on the edge and basically just start
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: attacking it. I stand because I have a range I can see it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I stand somewhere over here while I catapult. So you're talking about the main zone? Yes.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: because you're gonna have the ability basically to attack it with a full round of surprise with advantage
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: While it's lingering. That's the second Bramgrim Plum. No, no, no, no. That's yours. Let's sing that. You attack it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: um but i think yeah he's saying he's let's also use the stone as creative structure
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, but if we do that, the giant will wake up. You can do it in a sequence.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I want, if I feel sometimes first name, I will wake up.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You can do the fire giant and then the stone giant. Did that work? I don't...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Remember, so you go create capital. I didn't finish what I was trying to say. After I do that.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I cast Misty Step or Blink or something to Ghost Star Free the Giants. Right, I was saying that two of you could go deal with the Firehands.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Everybody deal with it. I think just go run it with both of them. For example, your Owlbear doesn't have Reign of the Past.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I mean the Owlbear can go try and figure out a way to... So the Owlbear can go help create the chaos on the stone.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We need to do the attack on the fire giant first so they can wake up. So here's what I'm suggesting.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the elder can go try and figure out a way to… So the elder can go help create chaos on the stone? We need to do the attack on the Fire Giant first, so it doesn't wake up. So, here's what I'm suggesting. Wait. So, wait… And we were about them.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We talked to the stone giants and let them know that don't attack and do possession.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: We're not going to attack them. The stone giants are in shackles, so they're not going to attack us. Yeah, we're trying to free them. We're going to free them first, and then we're going to...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Are they smart enough to understand those instructions? Are we able to pass them the text?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: yes but i mean yes you are yes the only thing is that the fire giants might notice that's the only yeah
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: But there are both and there are also all the mistakes that are not going to arrive in that list.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and these are self-checks you will have to make.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, Pass Without Trace. Alright, I'm just, I'm done with that. So, you need...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We feed them, and in the same way, we are going to signal the chaos.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: It's a time in your life and we're all going to be scared into attack.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Look, there's one guy, one guard at the front that I don't think will be able to see.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: that I don't want to risk our entire plan on.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I don't want to risk our entire plan on one saving throw. That's the issue. I want to- There's no saving throw.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Let's still check with the Bible. No, because we're in Gaspur.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: How are we going to sleep in Sunchai Fall or in Gatsbond? Akritas and Felubur
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and Ruler, Weewe, Misted. By the way, I'm assuming you've all taken the long routes, right? Yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we stay there and we'll be there. It'd be better if we didn't be Owlbear-free. If we Owlbear-complete, right? If we just, like, sit down.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I mean, they're all going to try to make me land a risk, so I'm going to have to fight to get help.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and Freed the Stunt-Guys, that's what I'm gonna say. Because that's what we need that people from the department to say.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Why would I need Pass Without Trace? It makes me step right over.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We need to do the 10-stick at will. That was that.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, I think you misunderstand my plan.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Who's the final team this week? Can I show you what I've got? Here's my plan. Can I explain?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: You guys drop out somewhere here. I don't go where you are. I stay here. Cast a spell on the giant.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: And then, uh, Kassa, Spell, this, top of the giant, you guys attack, and then
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I, me, and Grimfjord is the same, different, the same steps, but that's different already.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Why will we see the Sun Giants first? Because then we don't have to come back to see them.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: My issue with that is that
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Most of the part can go up here because they're still in the gas room. So why don't we do it simultaneously so I don't have to create those videos.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Akritas is one of the big damaging and it's having if you can have her have that advantage
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and a free like we both on the giant that's like a free 40 or 50 there it's
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I mean, it's a great movie, but that's why...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Free the Stone Giants, then do the rest of your plan with the rest of your project. Yeah, Free the Stone Giants, I-
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I can do that by myself. Me and the Owlbear can do that. But we need you to do the Owlbear first.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: That's why I dropped that like over here because I have to bring the game so you can understand.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Owlbear... Okay, so let's say Owlbear spins here, can't you... Or I get one of these giants like...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So, all the rest of us.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I mean right next to the giant. It's going to be not able to move. So it comes inside here.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, yeah. I cast a thing that's basically, like, right here. So, and you move here.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh no shit uh i i need to find a good spot that we go because i need to
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We can't do this, we have to do it online, sorry.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I need to be in the memory. Can I move these real quick?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: You might need to drop by in a little bit of a different spot, but it's okay.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Where's like the sun here? Where's the light? Where's that light?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what my life was.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: oh yeah all right so I can sneak a little bit of uh ah can I show you where to drop that
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: somewhere like right here because my it's a it says uh 20 so but
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: If I place it right there.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Can I show you my thing? Yeah, I see your thing. If I place it right here, that gets the fire giant.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: And it allowed me to go from here, line of sight, right.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: perfectly fierce I'm not in range of that so I can cast it and then jump and then go get one of the giants
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Hey, we want to do this. You got one?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I believe so, but I don't see any problem.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I dare to explain it to you.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's it. Can we play the plan? Yes, sir. All right.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Everd's Black Pentacles, cover that 20 foot square
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: The Grinding is still within range, so for about five.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh for the duration just just set for the record so that there's no confusion we will use the
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: They do not be underlaying grids, that will make the grid longer as well. What's your grid? I'm about to decline.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and just like oh that's good yeah that's the one okay uh we'll use the green
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So what I'm going to do is I'm going to cast it right here.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: so that the giant gets affected okay then what is going to happen
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I, using lines, I'm going to cast about this spot, but it can spread it over here, right?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So if I show you, line of sight from here allows you to be basically right over here.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: around here to that other 90 foot top anyway all right all right understand yep so we've been
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Can the Owlbear slay one of the giants? Like, to bite the chain off or something?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He can definitely try.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: so i'm going to be over here i'm going to cast that spell they're going to drop off here
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: oh because because the giant's going to be
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh they're gonna drop off right yeah they're gonna drop off like basically they're gonna be all drop off like
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: where they in a way they can attack the fire giant because the fire giant is going to be incapacitated
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and it's going to have the Restraint of Conviction so we're going to have advantage on it and let's go Thank you very much.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: While they're doing that, I'm, after that, I'm
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So immediately we're going to run over and start freeing the giants. Okay.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I'm also going to have Blink on myself, that way I have an easier way of escaping so that they can't...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So if the fire guy is trying to close the gap on me, they can't get me. Okay. Did that work? That is definitely a...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: That's definitely a workable plan, the outcome of which is ill-defined and unknowable at this time.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So let me go over it.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm going to draw a rectangle.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Something like this.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Get it in a good, I also have to get it in a good, something like, yeah, that's it, that's what we do.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Basically trying hard to focus the fire drive, because...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We're kind of in a little bit of a corner, so let's just kill it as fast as possible.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I think I can do it now. Is that good?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Let me just try and draw some other lines, be careful, see if your hands can get it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Do you have line of sight? Yes. Is it the line I just gave you, line of sight? Do you see it? Let's try it again.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Is that a line of sight?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: From where you are, where Felkur is right now. I'm just drawing the line. Yeah, yeah, that is what I was going to say. I'm actually going to move like that then, because...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's easier. Okay. Sorry. Now let me redraw one of the rest of them. I'm trying to draw a rectangle so that they look to me. I'm trying to draw a rectangle so that they look to me.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Legally Obvious. You want to make this? Yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: there you go like that i was mostly trying to see
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I was trying to see if there's a way I can get all of these to any...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: You can hear as well without having to. How big is this? 4 by 5.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Any extra room I'm just shoving off into the side of the corner.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So according to the rules that I have defined, the monster has to be at least half.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: but you could do it that way no but then we can't attack it
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: because it stays on the ground yeah everybody two people use melee
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'll make it one.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: oh yeah you can just all right except you're going to be actually you can jump to corner if you need yes you can walk so all right we're good we're good
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: The rule is you can always navigate on the bag. Alright, we're good. Ready? Is everybody ready?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Do you like that now, young man? Ah, we're good. You ready?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: After I cast it, do I have movement to run over?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Let's do one thing at a time. Okay, let's first of all get our initiative going.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, why don't we start like, okay, now that you've told me we've got a surprise round.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: i'm gonna give you guys a surprise thank you all right i don't should have asked that can we did we get a surprise round beforehand yeah
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to declare for the purpose of this combat.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: you've spent so much inordinate amount of time it's a good no no i don't know anything
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, I gotta get a bit of this in a roll. Yes.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: If, maybe, it's funny, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: and all those three bestowal guns.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Dude, this Owlbear went from a simple just random thing in the middle of the word
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: to literally going to the depths of hell and back, as it should be.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: We did not expect that.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I don't belong in other states.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what this location will appear after we make our plan well felt so far. Yes, I'm sure that is a witch.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You're so good at that.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know the story of the Lich, right? Yeah, that's true. So what happened was basically we were fighting...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: um uh i forget what it was and there's a couple skeletons and he would and you know there's
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Skeleton, that we just left off as, oh, an important skeleton. We were trying to get this vial that could start a zombie plague.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and so skeleton was this originally set in the beginning the skeleton was a rich
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: that time stopped, stole the vial, and teleported away.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's going to be there in about a minute. If one of these don't die, this is a lich.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You and me can do that. You can't go from the class.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Once something is done and it's a classic, you know, you've got to respect that. We good?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. I haven't given all the fire giants numbers.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Doohill and Venoth. Oh wait, if they're set up like that, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I might need to ask to...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I may have to redraw the square if you move some of the creatures around. I just got rid of the one that was near you.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Question, are the Helmets, will be Helmet Horror in this policy? Yeah, no.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: One is helmet of horror and the other one is helmet of horror making that just put a B next to it. Oh wait, now I can do it like this.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and I get all, every creature in. What? Wait, so there are two or three? There should be three.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: okay uh you see different names underneath them there we go i see different
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yefimov, Yefimov, and some others of the name and plus number one. Yeah, so Hellhound, Owlbear, Hobgoblin.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so do you remember the beginning of this? Yes, we remember the beginning of this.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: But in the specific order, it is going to be Thorax. What? In the specific order.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No, you want to put a B because they do different damage.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'll just, I'll take care of this, don't worry about it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so there's no stats for it, that's what I'm trying to tell you.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: See you later.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I should have played this while we were at Conspiracy.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so if I drop out, right?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: The reaction of every firefighter in the room right now.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: We may have a few different ones in a second, so we'll get rid of this now.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: All right, now every creature there is that they all have to make.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Wait, are we still?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Are we ready to start the combat? Yes. Everybody has to make a...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Fire Giant doesn't have to, but the other three have to make a beefy 19th string. Where do we start?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We're the gays, everybody- Hold on, we'll start- we'll start at the top of the initiative work. So I have a corny. So, Akritas?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Well, we can do it the following way. We can start, we can assume...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We assume that Akritas, we can give Felkur the first action.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Shouldn't we be able to have those prepared actions and things? Yes.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so I cast the spell. Okay. So fire trance makes a saving spell for those three. It's a DC 19.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Have you seen any team? Yeah. Thanks.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: do they make it on their turn or do they make it uh make it now and then every turn have to make it again
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: or else take 3d6 and they take 3d6 points of damage
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I rule very well. Really? Yes, I rule this 15 to 17 of 19.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Two of them are... No, that's what I ruled. I haven't checked their abilities yet. Oh, bruh.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: it's fine i only care about one of them don't care about the other guys you're trying to kill the fire giant
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: All right, all three of them made it. Good, lovely.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: What happened, Steven? Nothin'? Nothin'. Uh, uh, trap, hold on, uh... Same, same, same, that'll have to re-roll.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he's currently, ah, okay, he's currently
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so we need six points for Gaelic. And he takes one? Six points for Gaelic. Let me roll that. All right, let's roll that.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Wow, he takes five points of damage.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Ooh, this is not looking good for the good guys. Oh, it's fine. We have three get-packs to bring to George.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Do you know the one? Really? No, the first time I think. Oh, that's good.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so how much points of damage are we? The point of that spell is to do damage.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, weapons of damage?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the point of that spell is that the fire giant can't exactly move anywhere without being trapped. Basically, the fire giant-
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: It's going to be 4th. Let's spend a bunch of turns in there. And the chance that we get it stopped again and again. Of course, he does have a plus 8 for strength.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: that's fine okay all right so okay who goes next uh can i Scythe, Scythe, Scythe, Scythe, Scythe.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: dad dad can i end about can i end my uh supply of turn by going over
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Let me have this out there, start here, and turn on the fire, giant tube.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We're going to try and let the Owlbear free me, we're going to.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to also tell them that you freed Skoraeus? Yeah. So you're going to tell them?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Nerevenans Nerevenans Not the whole, the specific, like, yeah, just, just the quick gist of what Yeah, the quick gist
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Let the Owlbear free you and then go and help us.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Is that good? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's the entire reason we did this plan, so that I had time to basically... No, no, no, I get it, I get it, I'm just trying to...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Kandy, Aldo, Free I've decided yes Alright good, so I'm going to tap Blink on myself to go
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so roll a DC 17 strength check for the Owlbear.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: 17
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Owlbear shatters the stone giant's shackles. I call it to go for your friend.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: um the stone giant stand up rather than the stone giant
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: okay yeah yeah you're no free he gets doesn't get an action okay next
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Are you all, is everybody done?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All these Felkur. Yeah. All right. So Felkur. Who's next?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No, but Felkur goes, now you do all your reactions in initiative order. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: so uh i'm guessing we'll start yes oh you have a pen bad boy
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Grudna, What is all you do with your friends? I don't know.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So what?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: What a Creeper will do, Osmo, with everything.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Blast, Favored Foe, Blast, Rylzyn D'Arl.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: You better roll a credit roll. Uh, I'll be there in a row when we're done.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm so glad you missed your bed.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Um, that's it. Yeah, sorry. That's a bit of a game, so we have to complete all of them.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: We'll come back when you have the answers. We'll again, we'll again. Yeah, for advantage.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I knew the advance, that's why you go to the picture. Oh wait, why are there so many now? Okay.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I don't need a caption. It's either one or one.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, by the way, Bramgrim should use fear tokens.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Just like insta-spirit-guarding it up, dude.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to get the storylines done. I think probably it's not going to cast again at this time. Um, we should get...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We should have all of that. I'm gonna have the stone giants come up.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: because I don't want to antagonize the two fire dimes next to us because I think uh
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Actually, I might, I don't know if I should write because the fire tracks will leave
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So should I house those stone giants and attack those Slayer giants?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Or should I have him come up to the Kingfire Giant? There's a physical space problem. You want to fit? Yes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The Fire Giants have crossbows and rain weapons. So, go ahead and just have them attack. It's up to you. Alright.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: And I'm almost done.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Only twine? I'm not sure that's the correct one, because we have a lot of, you know, Oh, that's a good one, good, good, good.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, that's the one. Yeah, you're over critical, so 54 games total.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Simpsons 4. How much did he roll for Dwayne Maynard? Nine.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Excuse me! Owlbear? You're kidding me! What? You have one joke!
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: How many goals did you get for the play together?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what you mean by that, I can't do... Oh, great.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Even though I'm a Christian, it's sexual time, so... Alright, so now, what did it down to do now?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: It started in 98, 97, oh wow.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's Deng's turn, so that's easy. Alright, immediately just act and surge it up.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Hey, we're in the reaction. The question is, in the reaction, can we do the vortex for acne or not?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: So I can only do that with with a firecracker and a glass so I can't make a saving throw again until we all get an attack.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: There is no third in two points, so it is done to ASU. Okay. It's done, it's done.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Bramgrim will start with Garen Gould.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: No, I was thinking about Guardian of Faith, but they're already paid for suicide there.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We've used all that stuff, and I used to have done this with Tatooine.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: it's a classic we want to look at the goals of one turn this entire thing
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I was really trying to make a document based on my own experience.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Warth, but there's too many creatures inside here.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So, uh, first I will be talking to Seth Brogan.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: DC, Sergen, Wizard, Petraeus, and Perthes. All right, four of them, right?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: uh three of them i don't think number it's Thank you for your attention.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and the first just like we have let me just check if they're immune or resistant to oh my god is that down to 80
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Don't we need to pause for a second?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Well, you need to tell me two, because... Alright, so...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what is the effect? What is the spell that we'll be casting on them? Uh, 8-level speed, Dahlia...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We wanted to tell you in podcasting about...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I guess Aurelian Damocles was the other one? Yeah, no, no, that's fine. Okay. Aurelian Damocles and Necroc?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Can I say the other one? Yeah. Or it'd be funny. How many minutes do I have to roll?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: How many is Bramgrim? Two. The one will clean up and
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: In fighting, first of all was for the king, he blows it, and the second of all was for the diviner, he blows it.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: When it was feeling so dazed down, it was reaction.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: you know you burned your reactions yeah no because he's laughing
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: who sent down six to one people and they were having to do nothing since then. Yes, yes, yes, of course. All right.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what I'm supposed to think about that.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: we have three uh hero of the film four for kind of dc ah that's what we can turn the giants to do
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Well, the Stone Giants still stop attacking even if we... Let's, let's, let's get to, let's get through one thing at a time. Alright.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, are you guys all done? Uh, we're out of options.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's for a surprise round. Everybody did it. Okay, so now I'll give this to those first.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Akritas with his bow. All right.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: The higher giant wakes up.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Let me look at this one, let me look at this one, could I have left my pen in with one of those, one of these guys? That would definitely wouldn't succeed.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. Thank you Jojo. Do we still have add-ons to the battle?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Uhhhhh, I don't, Nick what does it con-
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Rishon, Everett's black tentacles, Leeds, and the restrain.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So the string, the condition, tax rolls against you have advantageous.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: All other stars have valid names.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Did you just say there is 12 damage? I think I need more.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Did you know I'm critical? I get it. Yeah. Because I'm red.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So I read 40 people, I see.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I'm going to walk away. Why don't you guys tell me where to find the counter and send us that one round.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I think it's over. Akritas hits more than 21 hit points right now.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, come on. Oh, come on. This is so funny.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, the bedside is still nice. Ha! Yes! I'll put you up.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Wow, it is. It was one good point. It's excellent. Absolutely. Welcome to your life.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I have an interesting piece to make. Actually, no, I'm not going to do that again. No, you can't. It's too far away.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, we do not, do not count me out yet.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no. I can still do it. You can do it. He's doing it. He's not going to have an opportunity to attack us.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Don't y'all have a couple- I have a couple uses of vicious modifiers.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Look, Daryl has got two, and he's up next. Oh, please, for the love of God, please do it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: PLEASE KILL THE VENETIAN DOCTOR! PLEASE DO IT! We will try, I'm not-
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We can do it, but we won't try. What's the fire drives?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: that's the fire giant's wisdom um i'm pretty high
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and you have a second attack which is to punch you in no no
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Cast the spell, it's a full action. Can you have a bonus action on punch?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Anyway, we need to please continue.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So, I'm going to cast blink on myself.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Actually, I'd rather shut this movie alone.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I might be bling because it's really useful for me to just not have to do anything.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh all right so then we're gonna go we're gonna test uh blink we're going to this giant is free right
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: This one's free, right? I'm going to go one.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Sig, I'm going to go here. I'm going to wave it out to my nuts.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Actually no, this will all resolve itself by itself probably, so I'm gonna go...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm trying to, it's pretty normal, it's still in there, right?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I miss both customer interaction. I can't see anymore.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a completely different one.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: You want to come closer and stop killing the other guys, don't do that. Yes.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Zangon question. Can I pistol? No, it's a bonus action.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: after spell or no? Because I can do it after firebolt, I can use my pistol and I use it my uh
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Can I use it after casting Blink on myself?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I have so many decisions, Dave. How do I go to the front and have them kill it with vicious mockery? It's a few minutes.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: yeah we do it we kill the fire giant king with uh vicious mockery all right so so what is it what was your question
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Never mind, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go over here.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I'm not- I'm actually not gonna cast Blink on myself but I'm just gonna go run over and free another giant. Okay. Uh, use, uh, Beach Tools.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Did you have them? Yeah, I think I had a couple. Were they after Lolth by the fan? Yes, they were after Lolth by the fan.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Natural 4 You're all a natural one
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I got this! Alright. I'm gonna just kind of stay, like, right up close. I'm gonna tell the giant, yo, can I like just stay right-
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I have partial coverage of that. I'm trying to stay right under it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: move over here and like or you can move behind the rocks like yeah I'm gonna assume that you can like yeah
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Die, please. Alright, so long. Number three, stay at home.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: who's that who's up next i don't think but he's still in prison right yeah all right so he rolls the strength check
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He can shatter the chains. He shatters the chains. He is now free. So he's now free.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, he moves his way. All right, who's next? Behemoth, number two.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, that's number two. We'll just take a swipe at Bramgrim.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, you're going to use it with, let's see.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Thanks.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on. I don't think we've done that. So, that's that TD20.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh the 17th what is uh what was one of these on both of them and the first one hits
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Toads
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: That's 15 points of damage plus an additional...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: 1d10, 3d10, 1d10, 1d10, 1d10, 20 points of damage.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Constitution, Seymour Thoreau, or Concentration, DC 10.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's a concentration saving throw by Willem for Conquer Constitution.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you made your constitution, same to you. Then again, it's the particular themes.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, the beginning is the list. Okay, number one is done. So you're going to try to break number two?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Um...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and those over there, and a toast to the great kings, compatriots, kings.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He does, so all the giants are in for free.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and you're going to move 10 more feet that way all right and it's thanks then yes okay
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We'd have to save that one.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I mean, I can list them all at once.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Are you going to try to kill it with a vicious mockery? I'm trying to find the song.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: about this exact thing and I can't
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, come on, reading. That's fine.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: So they think Vicious Morcane old? Yeah.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: You have to do a DC 14 wisdom saving throw.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The king dies as a...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He's dead. But, you know, I want to hear the... Oh my god, wait, wait, wait, wait.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I stand, it's your turn, will you stand up?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Atop the rock, baby, don't do this
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: The Blaskeed of Grace, Reckon me some peace.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes. Keep going.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: That's the first way to go, that's where I'm back in Cardinal, 1, 2, 4, take a snooze
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: In the Chalice of War's Windblow and Diplomatic Undo, 2014
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: We need to all do a challenge We just died to some words Oh, that's a good one. It's a good one.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you very much.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I have much more magic I could use instead.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: and Buck, Organic Scratch, and Pizza Pair for Blackies, Dad, Forest Lady, Y'all
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Sauron, Taklan, Matic, Anub, Onesie, Forbiddings, Sauron, Ereche Sarah
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: and I will be still first, let's go and check my magic out!
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Hmmmm...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, can we say that?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: all right okay wait what do you say to it
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: You're making fun of it and it takes care of it. What do you think?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Sage, the guy just is like, kill me now.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's what they did. Sing it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No, he's not going to say it. There's only so much we can ask. All right. Okay. Thank you for committing to the bill.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know the lyrics really, so thank you for committing to the Veth of Nidigvish's Locker. Yes, of course.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, so, uh, what happens next?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: It's pretty interesting. Yeah. Let's hear it for Owlbear.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Owlbear, yes. I mean, what do we do now? We're not too late, right?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: um well right now there's two fire giants this film's gonna fight yes
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: yeah um I mean you have to leave somehow
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So the only problem is we have to see what they tell the guy we're going to do. Yes.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, Owlbear just waits. Owlbear just waits. Owlbear waits.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Question, because it was between October 2010, does it have to be recorded for movement? Oh, yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I think that's advantage on a saving throw. Yes, of course. I think we should save first. Alright.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, Strength? Was it? What did I have to beat for the Ritsan Kulsnink?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh 19 and I failed and for
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He makes it. Can you take time down, please? We actually have some music in the mouth. Ooh, 13 points of damage!
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I don't know what you're talking about. I did Southdown, I'm sorry. Yes. But I was talking with a local.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Thomas Thomas Smith, everyone.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what that means, but I'm not sure how much time I have to take now. 13. 13.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: it's not a damaging spell but it's just strange so you have
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: The point of the spell was so that you have an advantage on it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and literally brought me in, you know, hey, Bramgrim, Decha, House Morcane, Decha, Rylzyn.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on, I'm just trying to think. I'll just have a roll of something to see if I've got it in the test.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so let's stop.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Are you trying to decide what Bramgrim is doing? Oh, Bramgrim is doing Garden of Spades.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, but then he loses his concentration. Why? Guardians of Faith is a concentration spell. Is it? It isn't?
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, there's a hobgoblin. I don't think so.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I don't think I can work for it.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: No, it's no, the concentration doesn't need concentration. Sorry. What?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay. I hope he hands us a duration of eight hours, because I'm not going to sit here.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh oh my god i can't believe we did that all right so you put
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna put it here so that all the creatures so everything
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: This is the reaction of the fire giant.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to the back of the cell. All right.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you have to run 3, 3, 17, 17, 17 first. I do.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, but let's just make sure it's on, when is that?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It has to start, it's on its turn.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: It's not now. Oh, it's on the creatures' plan? Yeah. Fine.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: okay who's uh who's up next i don't know i don't see that
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I just read it. It said, a large spectral guarded, make sure you're reading the players handbook 24 edition.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: 2014? No, 2024. Absolutely fine.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: 14 spell. So I don't know if I can see the presentation mark.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: uh no concentration okay great that's right
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: The only thing that changes is when he moves and grows.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So at the start of the creature's turn or when it enters the space?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: so uh design for by design number one again number one
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Let's go down and see this guy.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He does 21, he does 40 to 62 points of damage.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Omni Giant, Stone Giant, 62, yes, um, Stone Giant, Young Burner
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, who's the next one?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Firebat 1 on Stone Guide, I think it's actually Stone Guide number 3.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and then all right then stone giant number two
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Now free!
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It picks up a lock and throws it at stone driver number three.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I think this is basically impossible.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, the other two sidecams are done. Well, you will in a second. Why? Takes 15 points of damage.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Fifteen or Fifteen? Fifteen, it's a proper time to give it.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So, what you're saying is that you have three copies? The Hellhound War, alright. So, how about this?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna, how about this? We're gonna do this. Fire gents do 60 points of damage each round.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giants do... Stone Giants...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: we're just so we can keep track of it it's 60 and the other guys do
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: uh uh it's a 3d8 plus six and more
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Coming for order you need about $1,250 plus a bench.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, so just 30 points of damage.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, 30. Yes, a little bit to the tax. Okay. Alright, so just deduct the hit points.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Now remember, you guys promised to help free the giants.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you did. That's why I said you're going to care about this.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so Pilgrim and Floral are next.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, I don't care about this. Okay. Well, then I guess you go. All right.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: BC 1936 and BC 1737
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, does he lose? No, he doesn't. He's out in the rain. Oh, yeah. Fails both.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Faerzworld. So, it's very different from the Faith Guardian. The Faith Guardian of Faerzworld, yeah. Yes.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Nick, comments on the blackboard?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh oh by the way if it's uh restrained you can have this event to enroll the center but it would be that okay
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh actually it it is not boglo it yes all kinds of damage all kinds of damage
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Did you mark the 12 points? No. Did you mark the 20? Yeah. All right. I still haven't made my most effective plan yet.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Dainside No. 2 I'm just trying to think if the Hellhound can actually attack this round.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We have an advantage on attack. I know, but I just...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I just, I just see, does he, does he have a ranged attack?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: it's difficult terrain oh it could move right it's not difficult terrain it's not restrained
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, this is a typical train. A little bit half the restraint condition, please.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: If he blows the saving power, he's restrained. Otherwise, it's the restraint.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's a difficult terrain. Yes. Okay, cool. So he blew his thing and throws in his restraints. Yes. Oh my god.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Anyway, let's have a look where it's at. That's what I'm about to check. Are we just farming from now?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Hey, thanks for giving me that spell, by the way. I did not. This was not my idea.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I went back to the yard and it was this idea. No, I'm just like, are you guys having fun? Yeah. All right, thank you. In that case, this is a great...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: this is a great session all right so um i'll finish this comment yeah we should because i have to go for a run all right
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Giants, fire, number two. Wait, does that have a long clearance of that? No, it does not.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, fire giant number two does 60 points of damage.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Your leader is dead by the way stop it but giants hate each other
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So they're all going to attack after they're going to fight each other. Yes, but you made a promise to the stone giant king that you would free his slaves.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I should have done better
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I told the giants not to attack each other.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Anyways, we're leaving.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I didn't want to kill Devorah. Just for the record, the other plan when you kill...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All of them showed the head, you know, he's dead, maybe if everybody runs away it would have been fine, but anyway, keep going.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: That's what I tried to do!
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So how much would you say that was 60? Uh, 60 and then 30.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's 50 points of damage out of the pool, to fire the stone giant number one. 60, okay.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: That's the beginning of number one. The beginning of number one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, the game at number one, I made a saving throw, the same one, yes.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: But there's only three of these attacks we've done, right? So this is the last one, yes? No, it's the second one. Oh, okay, sorry.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: he blows it takes 20 points of damage and half the damage of the 12th part
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: uh no it doesn't take advantage because he made the same so he steps over here so that's ten movement five
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Ten, Fifty, now five-ten.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: there's a body in the way yeah it's he walked around all right 20 it's it's uh he gets here and he is now going to hit that
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: 14. What's your armor class? 21. That's a miss. 14. That's another. All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Roadmouse, Torbjörn, Spigdeggen Oh, dude! 2d20 has advantage on that. Veth
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And he blows it! Much damage.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so time of the order. Yes. Yes, so Akritas turn. Yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Put an arrow in number one, or in one of their, actually one of the chained ones.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Should we even have a queue? No, do the Helm of Horde, because that one's closer to death.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. No. It does 28.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: N'zazet Oathbone, 24
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: If you want to leave it for one of the spirit guardians, you can. 24 is dead.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I know I've guessed more than three points now, but that doesn't mean it's that important.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We are at 12, so one more please, Akritas.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: It's the exact same damage, no.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Why? Because we don't deal with that against Sorn and Nerevenans.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Snipe, Blast, Thirteen, Twenty, Two, Don't shoot, don't shoot, do you have a favorite phone?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, this is true, but I think I'm still gonna pass that. I think that's more biblical.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Even that has to do with Aromus 65.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: so it's the one hp all right you're vicious not going yet again that that's what no you did what
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: 22 plus five. Yeah, that's true. Okay.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Zeymoc Nevish, Mothraeid again, probably, all right, who's next?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: uh stone giant number three no me no so that's right oh my god what can we do
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: What do we do? Which one's still captured?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No one. Everyone's free. Everyone's free. We'll have to start killing the giants. Or killing the stone giants. One or the other.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Remember you have your cold devices.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I have to get there. Actually, no, I'm going to just start poking these guys.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: We go here, I'm just gonna shoot one of them. Okay, you climb up on the rock so that you're not-
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I'm just going to poke up my head and be like, haha. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: That's a good one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: 23 points are down for using the cool drone device, right? Then we're gonna just go duck back to that, right? Yep
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Let's poke our head up and poke our head down.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you've also got your canon.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: When I poke my head out, I go like over here, and then back, and then my hand goes one, two, three.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: and Cone and Enforced Whistler.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Ignore the fact that it's fire damage, I can't change it from a flash, as far as they're on the gear, sorry.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: fourth damage okay or 15 plus the damage okay four seven okay
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: yeah and does it be for the first for yeah
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: And it gets knocked back five feet. It gets knocked back five feet?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, which exposes into another 15 points of damage from the stone bed.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, who's next? I think that's number two.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what Damocles does. Hey, I'm going to save the throws. First he has to make a saving throw against Dixarity.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Dexterity? He makes it! No! Okay, so he doesn't take... Oh, he takes 10 downs. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and then the dexterity guy who blows the uh the other one and strength
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: No, no, oh wait, no, it's already made the strength one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He goes over here to step outside of the zone.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He makes a saving throw at the end of the turn. So first he attacks.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: He attacks twice, and misses both times. Alright, now it rolls for a saving throw.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: And this is the Saving Throes. He's still alive. Yes. I wish that was still jumping.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I think it's 39 and 36. I know. Did you subtract the... I'm doing 39. I'm doing it that way.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Please don't defend the six-feet-dome. All right.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giant number 1. Stone Giant number 1, those 30 points of damage to Fire Giant number 2.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Perfect? Yup. Okay. Done yet? Alright.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, let's see, Fallen Lands was a number of a long place.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: The King, Wonderwall, Os, Kip, Scyth, Gaelic, The Magician, The Christian, The Spirit
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Nerevenans, that was, first of all, peace, welcome aboard.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, there's a new subplot. Are we at subplots? I'm repassing 20.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So that's only 12 quick points.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Bramgrim said something about you have to be a bard, don't you?
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: I don't have a third attack, I don't have a third attack, I don't have a third attack. Yes, that's why you don't have a third attack!
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, who's next? I didn't say she's not going under that. I didn't have a chance to go under it.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Who's next? Owlbear. By the way, I think Vicious Mochrie has a donut section. Kennedy is from afar.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Well, you're saying words like...
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Yo Ugly, oh it's an action, it's not an intersection, all right.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Uh, Owlbear, and I don't want him to go die.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Owlbear charges. Why did you say that? Because that's what owlbears do.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Did you ask me? Is this thing number one or number two?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: well number two it's got two stone bands number one's got one stone guy
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So it's still going to be number two, right? All right. The last three I've heard, the last ones are twins.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: That's a noose. That's a hit.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So, 13.2 number 2, right? Yep, 10 number 2.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Bramgrim
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: And Bramgrim, Bramgrim, Brambley. Uh, we'll...
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: How many minutes do we have? How long have we been on the Stone Giants?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: the stone giants can like move away if they don't want to die but like you know i guess you're gonna use uh
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: What we don't have is...
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: He's gonna do something bad, I guess, if you remember.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: So you have to deal with them several times.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Glow, Nusim, Groth, Ornani, Klee, Degs, Klandi, Orn, Artis, Dantut, Trikut for instance
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I accept that you didn't mean to do any product damage. Didn't Veth know? Well, you didn't ask.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: So, we are going to keep going? What? Yeah, no damage.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Who's next? Uh, let's see, Firegiant number one. Alright, Firegiant number one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: That does 60 points of damage to stone deck number three.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giant Number 2 does 30 points of damage to Giant Number 2, Fire Giant Number 2.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Hound Boar, the singular Hound Boar
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: has to make a bunch of single girls yes it has to do the dexterity and the special
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the strength one, he fails and dies.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So, they say it's still alive. Yeah. I'm just kidding.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right, who's next? I just think that's a fire giant.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Behemoth, the fire giant number two, does 60 on the stone giant, oops, notice he has to get some shoes
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It attacks a stone giant with 60 points on the stone giant. Where is the stone giant? Number one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Alright, who's next?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: The 15th number one. The 15th number one. Attacks die. She has a USA.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Yeah, that makes sense. It does.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: All right. Big simple to damage. He attacks twice.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and the second attack hits for 3d10
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: No, but three of the cabinet for 27 points of damage.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and he makes his eight wisdom saber girl okay uh so wait dayan takes 24 27 yes
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: I'm 73 and this is the number one, right? Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Apex, Apex 10, and Apex 7, Apex 8, and Apex 9.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Akritas turn. Yes. Akritas will attack Nazgûl.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: All right, it's the same, one number for two.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: And so we do so we like me already.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Hi, Lightning and Arrow. Thanks a lot, Lightning and Arrow. Do that.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: And he's dead. He's dead? Number two is dead.
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: All right, number two is dead. Yes, but it's in costume number 101, Barthelm, and Klaipas.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and that's the 5th or 10th place.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: and Hedwins. Stone Zion number three and one.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: They're three and one, right? Yeah. Stonejoy at number three and one. Stonejoy at number three disengages.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. That decides to go over here. Can I move on?
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: So giant number one smashes fire giant number two for three points of damage.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: You fired a stone dart, right? I fired a stone dart, yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and it's Dynas, yeah, okay.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Dein, Pastor Peter, No.1
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Fers, Bats, Bees, Serpent, Elven, Wip, Saddle, Soul, Thor, Thorpan
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: There are two points and number one is dead.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Well, how many rounds did they spell down? Which one? They only went for the people who- Oh, one minute. Ten minutes. For which song?
SPEAKER_02 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: We have one that we have kind of stuck ourselves inside the room because we cannot go outside.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: You can dismiss it as a bonus action or as an action. Uh, I'm sorry.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Can I dismiss it? It was fine. Okay, you can get out.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Where Akritas is, she can get out of there. Yeah, but I'll take benefits then. Oh, you want me to get you out of the castle so I can use the... You can go through Bramgrim.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: i can also cast all in the wall no i'm just telling you i can cast off all in the wall if that helps
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Can you see how far I can go? Do you want me to try stop at Pass Wall? No, you don't have to go that far.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: How do you do the roundup? Two. Two? Yeah. It's always two plus two. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: So we can go here? Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Um, Owlbear.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Two new clients are around now. Their loot is almost dead, so we've got to keep killing them now.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: It's in so many settings, but that one's funnier. That's a deal.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, Solom, Hellhound, Owlbear, Oh no, I didn't want to go out. No. I didn't... Little stone giants are dead. Oh, they're dead.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Bramgrim. Wait, did he skip my turn?
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we think we did. Go for it. Sorry, yeah, you know, I could've got... I could've got you guys all out. It's fine.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: We have to do everything and see the fight. Yes, that's why it would have been useful because I can cast Hold the Wall and you can get through.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: I know, you want me to cast the hole in the wall? Yeah. Cool, there's now a hole that allows me to get through here.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Is that the bonus section or in action?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: That's an action, it's fine. I don't have a kill spell I can use. Because of one of the things that was going to be there.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: You have heal spells, you don't think you have them yet? Yeah, I have the mage to heal it though. Yeah, I have a touch heal spell.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Veth, Stealth Stone Yeah, I can't Okay, it's fine If you want to have a call, Bramgrim can come through and Yeah, that's right Yeah, that's right Veth, Stealth Stone Yeah, that's right
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: It's 20 feet deep, so...
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, this is 20 sleep, yeah. Yeah, very good.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Gahram, Bramgrim, thing number one. Yeah, I think...
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: If he's got, um, do they have game to order?
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Felstermass, Feehord, Felstermain, Felstermass, Feehord
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Sixty-eighths already.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: uh well let's go to them for one
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: Never mind, I owe it. Au revoir. My sleeping world.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Please, for 38 quick months, manage one as much as you would like. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: We're in number one, right? Yeah. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: Kostadis Roussos: I guess it's fire giant number one fire giant number one
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: and just as fire giant number one as you guys didn't notice her but Velastro walks in and casts banishment on him
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yes, the revenants.
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: So, lovely! Ah, what a lovely...
SPEAKER_03 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: and screams, where is Dendro?
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Is that the guy we just killed? Yes.
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: we'll stop here fire chat
SPEAKER_00 [?]: Kostadis Roussos: Can I say he wasn't the one who killed? I don't remember.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Number one did it. The other giant did it. That guy did it. We can point to the other guy and say, he did it.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: That's stupid!
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Did we kill their BBEG too fast? Did we need something else to do? No, I was thinking, what would she be doing? She would be charging straight at Dengar.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: Wow, that wasn't the fire giant that you needed. That wasn't the fire giant that killed you.
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: That's the key, because that confuses me into the plot for my game, which I can't roll!
SPEAKER_01: Kostadis Roussos: THREE CLUTCH NOT TWENTYS! Or she figures out it's Solom, or you can send her back to Solom.
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: You don't actually own that pen. You know what's the problem with that?
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but the problem is that if she dies...
SPEAKER_02: Kostadis Roussos: Who is the son of Dermot? Well, she's gonna come back. Yeah. Hey.
SPEAKER_03: Kostadis Roussos: i'm just telling you you have options so a good so a good four and a half hour d&d fitness where do you see me come up you see